Shivangi Srivastava

- Email shivi7.avi@gmail.com
- Mobile 91+09711454317
- LinkedIn URL -www.linkedin.com/in/shivangi-srivastava-0b421b8b
- House no. 537 3rd floor sector 46 Gurgaon Haryana 122001, India

A professional with dependable experience of 7yrs in financial services and analytics adhering to FP&A and Investment and Insurance Accounting. Received star performer in Accenture in 2016 for excellence in projects and promoted to Analyst from Associate in June 2017 in a team of 250 employees. Received several Shout Outs for outstanding performances in Projects in BLACKROCK like Regression Testing and Migration of various processes. Promoted to Associate in Jan 2021 for the exemplary performance and People manager's role in 2022 with team of 4. Core member of BLACKROCK Gives team which creates impact by giving back to the society and actively participating in various events.

Core Skills and Competencies

Financial and Management Reporting | Variance Analysis | Statutory Reporting based on US GAAP and IFRS | Reconciliation of NAV | Client Reporting and Stake holder management | Financial Report Analysis | Business Analysis.

A problem solver rather than task completer | Positive attitude and Good Organisational Skills.

Technical Acumen

FP&A Software's - Hyperion | Essbase | SmartView | IBM Cognos TM1 | SAP | Tableau | Global Sales Reporting tool. Along with Aladdin technical Platform by BLACKROCK.

Work Experience

BLACKROCK • Gurgaon • India

Financial Planning Associate

01/2021 - 09/2023

- Led a team of eight people in implementing and executing insurance services for a new client from APAC locations, successfully transitioning the other client simultaneously to other team member within two months.
- Managed a team of four as a People Manager since April 2022, overseeing their performance and development.
- Being part of recruitment team, conducting and managing the selection of suitable candidates for the team and implementing training sessions for their growth and development pathways.
- Worked on pricing and data streamline for the new client, implementing accuracy for price validation and market values. Reviewed aged breaks and collaborated with functional teams to ensure timely updates.
- Prepared daily management review dashboards and actively participated in conference calls with clients.
- Contributed to the AUM and Revenue Analytics team in an IC role by delivering key metrics such as AUM, NNB, and NNBF, supporting revenue attribution and planning modelling and analytics which is a part of FP&A team and focuses on revenue actuals for the USCA Wealth Advisory business across different tranches, such as Open End Funds and Close End Mutual Funds.

Prepared detailed revenue analysis reports on a weekly cadence and conducted variance analysis on a
monthly basis, presenting findings to senior management. Created process documentation from scratch
to effectively communicate findings and process mechanics.

BLACKROCK • Gurgaon, Haryana, India

Financial Analyst

09/2018 - 12/2020

- As an Analyst targeted monthly, quarterly, and annual reports for various clients, with a primary focus on my client. Reconciled NAVs on a monthly basis and conducted thorough validation and research on breaks, utilizing inputs from other IAG teams. Created templates and extracted relevant information for client communication.
- Actively participated in client calls, providing information on the Aladdin Accounting Portal for client, while also performing manual tasks as required by the client.
- Successfully migrated to the Aladdin Client Report (ACR) using ADAM X, replacing the Mail Manager tool
 for global locations. Also eliminated task Oracle Financial service vendor team to BLACKROCK creating
 team in the APAC region, ensuring task completion during regional holidays.
- Led the migration of the Aladdin environment to the Aladdin External Network (AEN) for exclusive Investment Accounting clients in the globally.
- Provided major support in training to new joiners for the Mumbai team in 2019 and took on leadership responsibilities in the Gurgaon location.

Accenture • Noida Area, India

Financial Analyst

12/2015 - 08/2018

- Collaborated as a team member of the COE Team, focusing on Europe sales reporting and analysis, with a
 reporting cadence of daily, weekly, and month-end reports, as well as ad-hoc reports tailored to client
 specifications. As an Individual Contributory, actively contributing insightful ideas and strategies to
 enhance communication and streamline report generation processes.
- Assessed financial statements and conducted in-depth analysis of sales revenue, costs, and expenses for clients, including projections for sales and revenue generation. Created comprehensive spreadsheets to identify trends and develop accurate forecasts, while also consolidating and analysing monthly results and budgets.
- Demonstrated dynamic and results-oriented leadership, consistently delivering excellent client service management and contributing to business development initiatives by trouble shooting techniques and quality assurance checks to uphold data sanctity.

Education

Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University, Kanpur • Kanpur • India

Finance - M.Com **07/2011 - 07/2013**

Chhatrapati Shahu Ji Maharaj University, Kanpur • Kanpur • India

Commerce - B.Com **07/2008 - 07/2011**

Huddard High School • Kanpur • India